A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Ann C. Whitman - Politics, Series P FA351
Rockefeller Archive Center
- R General (Box 16, Folder 377)
  Rowen, Henry S.: 1968, President, The Rand Corporation, NAR support of study on retrieval and utilization of information with the U.S. Government for national security. Rowley, James J.: 1966-1973, appeal to NAR for St. Joseph College, retirement party for Mr. Rowley. Rozell, Edwin H.: 1967, Editorial Director, "Poughkeepsie Journal," retirement. Rozendahl, Kay S. (Mrs.): no date, personal correspondence. Rubin, Jay: 1959, President, New York Hotel Trades Council, Hotel Trades unions minimum wage. Ruge, Daniel F.: 1967-1968, Director, Washington Office New York State Department of Commerce, Federal Administration vs. State. Ruiz, Luis Emilio Gomez (Dr.): 1959, Banco Mercantil & Agricola, Caracas, Venezuela; NAR sympathy on loss of son. Rusch, Claire: 1969, thank you for helping Mrs. Rockefeller select fall and winter wardrobe. Rusk, Dean: 1961-1969, U.S. Secretary of State, Brazilian-American relations, Soviet-American relations. Ruxin, James K.: 1970, Dartmouth reunion, sends photos. Ryan, William H. (Jr.): 1973, Republican politics, NAR letter on Mr. Ryan's retirement and testimonial dinner.
- Ramos, Manuel, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 378)
  79th District, Bronx County, Issues of New York State.
- Randolph, Jennings, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 379)
  Chairman, Committee on Public Works, United States Senate, National Commission on Water Quality.
- Rashap, Arthur W., 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 380)
  Legislation for Park, gift/lease back, New York Committee to Reelect the President, Inc., Federal Bureau of Investigation meeting, corporate contributions.
- Raskin, Abe, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 381)
  Assistant Editor, Editorial Page, "The New York Times," "Home Town Plans," resistance to the admittance of blacks.
- Ray, Sandy F., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 382)
  Minister, Cornerstone Baptist Church, insurance policy to be reinstated, appeal to NAR, suggestion to avoid another Attica.
- Reagan, Ronald, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 383)
  Governor of California, visit to New York, March 1967, Medicaid program, Republican Governors' Conference, Palm Springs, list of gifts, personal correspondence.
- Reed, Joseph V., Jr., 1969-1973 (Box 16, Folder 384)
  Vice President, Assistant to the Chairman, Chase Manhattan Bank, David Rockefeller's plates for vehicles in his use, David Rockefeller's "Outing for Public Officials."
- Revson, Charles H., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 385)
  Chairman, Revlon, Inc., NAR's thank you for gifts for Republican Governors' wives.
- Riesel, Victor, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 386)
  Publishers-Halls Syndicate, press release "New Northern Strategy," Mr. Riesel thanks NAR for good wishes.
- Robb, Charles S., 1968 (Box 16, Folder 387)
  President, University of Virginia School of Law, Mrs. Robb thanks NAR for flowers, NAR visit to Charlottesville.
- Robb, Gene (Mrs.), 1971 (Box 16, Folder 388)
  Thanks NAR for appointment to Hudson River Valley Commission.
- Robbins, Gordon (Mrs.), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 389)
  NAR thank you for shopping guide to Paris.
- Roberts, Albert B., 1972 (Box 16, Folder 390)
  Secretary, Assembly Ways and Means Committee, New York State Assembly Chamber.
- Robertson, Mrs. Cliff (Dina Merrill), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 391)
  NAR's sympathy on loss of her mother and son.
- Robinson, Jackie, 1962-1972 (Box 16, Folder 392)
  Executive Vice President, Chock Full o' Nuts Corp., NAR contribution to Baptist church destroyed by fire in Georgia, NAR marriage and political future, Southwest Conference on Poverty, two-party system, Negro political appointments, Freedom National Bank sale of shares, news conference by NAR at 22 W. 55th Street, project housing minority area, letter to NAR about loss of confidence in NAR--includes NAR's reply.
- Robison, Daurice (Mrs.), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 393)
  Re: adoption, NAR's recommendation.
- Rockefeller, John D. 3rd, 1959-1973 (Box 17, Folder 395)
  New Provision State Dormitory Authority; Lincoln Square Center, Lincoln Center Board of Directors Meeting; NAR declines Rockefeller Foundation dinner; NAR thanks Mrs. John Davison Rockefeller 3rd for support to National Campaign Headquarters; Ivy League Dinner, John Davison Rockefeller 3rd declines to be speaker; Invitation to NAR to spend weekend in Williamsburg; NAR congratulations on Lincoln Center fund campaign surpassing goal; planning in the Lincoln Square Area; Abortion Law; Homes for Managment in Pocantico to free houses inside estate for use of members of the family; NAR thanks for John Davison Rockefeller 3rd's contribution of Ray Lamontage services to campaign; John Davison Rockefeller 3rd contribution to Whitney Committee: Inaugural festivities; Page Payne; NAR's recommendation of Donna Mitchell to John Davison Rockefeller 3rd; NAR offer to John Davison Rockefeller 3rd for "The Trial of Major Andre" artwork; Rockwood Hills; NAR advises John Davison Rockefeller 3rd on security plan for the estate; Council on the Arts; appeal by John Davison Rockefeller 3rd to NAR; NAR appeal to John Davison Rockefeller 3rd re: help from Foundation to Portugal primary and secondary education; Gypsy moth spray, Pocantico Hills; Saving in operations of Kykuit and Pocantico Playhouse; Rockefeller Family gathering; Commission on Population Growth; John Davison Rockefeller 3rd congratulations to NAR and thanks for tour of Albany Mall; correspondence re: Urban Development Corporation program in Town of Greenburgh, Westchester County; Bush Foundation, Minnesota; population control; NAR congratulations to John on book; John Davison Rockefeller 3rd appeal to NAR re: Channel 13 (Public Broadcasting System); John Davison Rockefeller 3rd's Urban Home Ownership Corporation appeal to NAR; John Davison Rockefeller 3rd thank you for meeting in Albany before NAR's term is up.
- Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1959-1973 (Box 17, Folder 398)
  Fred Morrow, White House Staff; New York State Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commission; Girl Scout meeting; fallout shelters and radiation detection instruments; Rockland Lake North Development; Outdoor Recreation for America Report to Congress and the President; Parks commissions; accessory cost and Executive Director salary underwritten by Laurance Spelman Rockefeller for Saratoga Performing Arts project; Laurance Spelman Rockefeller's contribution to John D. Rockefeller, Jr's Scholarship Fund; Laurance Spelman Rockefeller appeal to NAR re: Orange County tax bill; Westchester roads; water pollution bond issue; Croton Aqueduct Park; problem of storage of atomic waste; NAR thanks to Laurance Spelman Rockefeller and Mary for record player & stereo; loan of art pieces, eastern museums; opening new wing Mauna Kea Beach Hotel; gifts; references of Nina Jones; memo on Rockwood Hall sale; NAR appeal to Laurance Spelman Rockefeller for Joslin Foundation; summary of New York City Program; Citizen Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality; Commission on the Future of Man; re: dedication of the Memorial Hospital for Cancer and Allied Diseases; congratulations to Laurance Spelman Rockefeller by Richard Nixon.
- Rockefeller, Laurance S., 1959-1973 (Box 17, Folder 0398A)
- Rockefeller, Martha Baird, 1963-1970 (Box 17, Folder 399)
  Article from "Journal American," NAR thank you for contribution to campaign; NAR thank you for Christmas present.
- Rockefeller, Martha Baird (Box 17, Folder 0399A)
- Rockefeller, Mary Todhunter Clark, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 400)
  Condolences on death of Winthrop Rockefeller.
- Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1959-1973 (Box 17, Folder 402)
  List of European party; Ed Love message to NAR; Hundred Year Association honoring John Davison Rockefeller 3rd, 1959; NAR letter to fellow Republicans on Civil Defense Commission radiation detector; Foreign Consuls meeting; remarks on collecting art; Civil Service Independents party; house lots in Pocantico Village; reactions to Rockefeller proposal to crack down on drug pushers.
- Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box 17, Folder 0402A)
- Rockefeller, Rodman C., 1960-1973 (Box 17, Folder 404)
  NAR thanks for campaign job; person to head entire area of minority groups; Venezuela purposes & objectives re: International Basic Economy Corporation; luncheon American Institute of Consulting Engineers; International Ladies Garment Workers Union Housing Project in Ruerto Rico; Rodman and New York State Council of Churches; International Basic Economy Corporation Finance Committee; Paraguay interest in developing relations with International Basic Economy Corporation; Thanksgiving meeting; International Basic Economy Corporation 25th Anniversary Dinner.
- Rockefeller, Rodman C., 1960-1973 (Box 17, Folder 0404A)
- Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1959-1972 (Box 17, Folder 405)
  NAR declines invitation to auction; results of Rockwin Fund Water Study Grant; NAR use of Winthrop Rockefeller's plane trip to California; Winthrop Rockefeller joins Governors Club, January 1967, taking office as Governor of Arkansas; NAR appeal to Winthrop Rockefeller to accept speaking invitation at Brotherhood in Action Dinner New York City; "The Future of the South," Winthrop Rockefeller address at Johns Hopkins University; Arkansas Turnpike Authority problems; Winthrop Rockefeller thanks to NAR for support in his campaign; Winrock Cattle Sales.
- Rockefeller, Winthrop (Box 17, Folder 0405A)
- Rockefeller, Winthrop Paul, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 406)
- Rogalin, John & Wilma, 1962-1971 (Box 17, Folder 407)
  Vice Chairman, Republican State Committee, Federation of Women's Republican Clubs, Mrs. Rogalin's activities.
- Rogers, Lucille, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 408)
  Executive Secretary to Governor of Florida Claude Kirk, sends unlisted phone numbers.
- Rogers, William, 1959-1972 (Box 17, Folder 409)
  Attorney General, Stockholm Conference worldwide environmental problems, NAR appeal for Kitty Carlisle Hart position United Nations.
- Romney, George, 1965-1973 (Box 18, Folder 410)
  Governor of Michigan, New York Young Republican Club Annual Dinner; National Conference of Christians and Jews; remarks of Governor Romney to Rhode Island Republican Dinner, March 1966; Annual Republican Student Leadership Conference, East Lansing, April 1966; Salute to General Clay Republican Dinner, Civic Center, Lansing April 1966; Detroit's Presenters International Olympic Committee, Rome, Italy April 1966; Fifth Annual Drake Law Alumni Dinner, Iowa March 1966; 45th Annual Massachusetts Safety Conference, March 1966; Kansas Press Association, Kansas March 1966; National Association of Purchasing Agents, Detroit May 1966; 14th Annual Republican Women's Conference, Washington May 1966; All America Cities Award Banquet, May 1966; Michigan Conference on Education, May 1966; Republican Appreciation Dinner, Nebraska May 1966; Nassau County Republican Dinner, May 1966; Governor's remarks on three and half years in office; Lincoln Day talk; Hartford speech; People to People Program; Race for Presidency Nomination.
- Ronan, William J., 1959-1973 (Box 18, Folder 411)
  Secretary to Governor; study of the Executive Branch New York State Government. 1961 Legislative Program, reorganization program; Land Acquisition Problem in Syracuse; designation of Board of Social Welfare and Committee of Scowl Welfare; Commission for International Official Visitors, 1963; Pure Waters Bond Act, 1965; remarks by William J. Ronan at Empire State Chamber of Commerce Businessmen Conference, December 1965; confidential letter on Ross Perot; personal correspondence.
- Ronan, William J. (Box 18, Folder 0411a)
- Roosevelt, Franklin, Jr. (Mrs.), 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 412)
  Chinese collection, Mr. & Mrs. Mottahedah.
- Rosen, Richard, 1966-1969 (Box 18, Folder 413)
  Assistant to the New York Hall of Science in Flushing Meadow.
- Roseman, Samuel I. (Judge), 1970 (Box 18, Folder 414)
  Suggestions on campaign issues, narcotic issues.
- Root, Oren, 1959-1967 (Box 18, Folder 415)
  Special Assistant, Steering Committee, Washington, 1959; Mrs. Root thanks to NAR; Taft Institute of Government, Biographical information on Dan Ruge; various tasks assignment to Mr. Root by NAR, Nixon trip to New York. Legislation on banking, Banking Department problems, Pension review project.
- Rosenthal, Benjamin, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 416)
  United States Congressman, Effective Administration Public Assistance.
- Ruebhausen, Oscar, 1959-1973 (Box 18, Folder 417)
  Debevoise, Plimpton & McLean. NAR insurance problems; Yonkers Raceway vs. fallout protection; Civil Defense; steps to take after 1968 nomination; City University Construction Fund; Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory; successor Chairman Atomic & Space Development Authority; Breeder Reactor; Special Study; Scott Commission; proposed inquiry into the purposes, functions and structures of Democratic Government to Meet Needs of Modern Society.
- S General (Box 18, Folder 418)
  Saarinen, Aline: 1963-1969, report, interview with NAR, TV show on NAR art. Sanford, Bill: 1966, thanks to NAR. Santo, Mary: 1971, visit. Sarnoff, David: Chair of the Board, RCA Corporation, Western Hemisphere Day, personal correspondence. Sauer, Benjamin: 1959, City Councilman, Syracuse (New York). Savarese, Anthony P.: 1966, sends resume. Scanlon, Rob: 1972, seeks position with Westchester County Parkway Police. Scelsi, Michael: 1966, NAR thanks. Schaetzel, J. Robert: 1966-1967, U.S. Representative to the European Communities. Scherer, Paul A.: 1962, President, Cosmos Club, refusal of membership for Carl Rowan. Schiff, Dorothy: 1965, Publisher, "New York Post," support for bond issue. Schmidt, Augusto Frederico: 1959, Operation Pan-America. Schmidt, Augusto Frederico (Mrs.): 1965, condolences. Schneider, Richard: no date, reporter, requests NAR reference for job application. Schoeneck, Charles: 1967-1969, Chairman, New York State Republican Committee, political campaigns. Schott, Bette: 1966, Montana bus crash, thanks for help. Schreiber, Heinrich: 1968, New York Trust, "Great Chain." Schroeder, Frederick A.: 1963, primitive art collection. Schuman, William: 1962, New York State Arts Council. Schwartz, Emmett: no date, sends resume. Schwartz, Maurice: 1959, candidate for Mayor, Auburn, New York. Schweibert, Erwin: 1965-1967, Assistant to the president of College of Idaho, NAR visit to Idaho, sends clippings, seeks appointment with NAR in New York City. Sears, Gerald: 1966, NAR thanks for photo. Sehneet, Lloyd (Mr. & Mrs.): NAR thanks for visit. Selden, Sabella: 1968, thanks for NAR. Seldon, Earl W.: 1968, Dartmouth reunion in Venezuela. Sells, Charles H.: 1966, child support problems. Seo, Helen: 1966-1971, thanks for Christmas gifts. Sevilla-Sacasa, Guillermo: 1962, Nicaraguan Ambassador to the United States. Sevits, Hyman: 1967, support for NAR. Seymour, Whitney North: 1967, South Street Seaport proposal, politics.
- S General (Box 18, Folder 419)
  Shafer, Raymond: 1968, Christmas gift. Shank, Donald: 1960, Institute for International Education, Standard Oil & Union of Soviet Socialist Republics. Shapiro, George M.: 1962, Laurance Rockefeller's investment in Israel. Sharaf, Frederic A.: 1968, recommendation. Shattuck, Edward (Mrs.): 1965, condolences. Shaw, Mel: 1968, New York State Young Democrats, admiration for NAR. Shaw, Robert: 1973, Republican Governors Conference. Sheffer, Hiram F. (Mrs.): 1960, thanks to NAR. Sheperd, Howard C.: 1962, invitation from NAR to serve on corporation, declined. Sherer, Samuel: 1959, Assistant to the President, United Air Lines. Sherwin, Louis: no date, thanks to NAR. Sherwood, Arthur W.: 1967, Baltimore (Maryland) politics. Shipley, Carl L.: 1961, chairman, District of Columbia Republican State Committee. Shriver, R. Sargent: 1961, Director, Peace Corps, job for Art Massolo. Shuster, George: 1960, President, Hunter College, retirement, copies of Long Island & Albany patents, purchases of territory from Indians 1685, 1686. Simplot, J. R.: 1965, Venezuela. Simpson, William K. (Mr. & Mrs.): 1960-1970, Christmas gifts. Sinatra, Nancy: 1967, tour of Metro Goldwyn Mayer. Single, Erwin A.: 1968, Editor, "New Yorker Staats-Zeitung und Herold," origins of Rockefeller family in Germany. Singletary, Sam: 1967-1969, National Institute of Social Sciences, State Office of Urban Affairs. Sivertson, Wilma: 1962, Republican politics. Skelly, Ned: 1967, Legislative reception. Skouras, George (Mrs.): 1962, Ogden Reid. Skouras, Spyros: 1963-1968, Chair, 20th-Century Fox Film Corporation, Hellenic University, personal. Slim, Mongi: 1960, Tunisian United Nations Ambassador. Sloane, Joseph C.: 1968, Ackland Art Center, Roger Stevens for job with Fine Arts Endowment. Slote, Leslie: 1966-1968, NAR thanks, 1968 campaign aftermath.
- S General (Box 18, Folder 420)
  Smith, Carleton Sprague: 1962, former President of Brazil Kubitschek's visit to United States. Smith, D. W.: 1965-1966, President, General Precision Equipment Corporation, politics. Smith, Edwin V.: 1960, thanks to NAR. Smith, Fred: 1967-1969, personal, wants to write book. Smith, George P.: 1973, recommendation for Cosmos Club. Smith, H. Alexander: 1959, Assistant Secretary of State (United States). Smith, Henry P.: 1967-1968, U.S. Representative, Erie Canal Sesquicentennial. Smith, Jack: 1967, Assistant to Governor Kirk of Florida. Smith, James: 1959, personal correspondence. Smith, Mason Rossiter: 1968, NAR campaign aide, seeks ambassadorship. Smith, Samuel: 1965-1968, Secretary for Education, Board of Missions of the Methodist Church, sculpture, political support. Smith, Victor: 1969-1970, political supporter. Smith, Ward: 1967, United States-Ecuador dispute. Smylie, Robert: 1965-1967, Governor of Idaho, Republican Party Committees, speeches, Goldwater article. Smyser, Craig: 1967, friends ask to see NAR art. Snyder, Murray: 1962-1967, National Security leak. Retraining semi-skilled workers. Soffey, Judy: 1992, NAR thanks. Solinger, Janet W.: 1968, Nixon Administration job for friend. Somoza, Anastasio (Gen.): 1967, President-elect of Nicaragua. NAR courtesy call. Spaeth, Carl: 1967, Stanford Law School, former staff, Vietnam, 1968 Presidential race. Spagnola, Gene: 1968, "New York Daily News." Spahr, Gene Hopkins: 1965, personal correspondence. Spear, Murray: 1967, Rockefeller fan. Speckert, Thomas: 1970, NAR daughter's trip to Paris. Spellman, F., Cardinal: 1960, thanks to NAR. Spencer, John: 1963, NAR get well wishes. Speno, Edward J.: 1966-1968, labor affairs, 1968 Presidential race, multiple party endorsements, state lottery. Spivak, Lawrence E.: 1959, thanks to NAR. Sprague, J. Russell: 1959, politics. Spratling, William: 1962, thanks to NAR.
- S General (Box 19, Folder 421)
  Stans, Maurice: 1969, U.S. Secretary of Commerce, seeks Washington job for assemblyman's son. Stanton, Frank (Mr. & Mrs.): 1970, Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS) Report on South Mall, personal. Steers, Newton I.: 1965, Maryland Republican State Committee. Stein, Henry J.: 1967, sent clippings. Steinbrink, Meier: 1965, Judge, NAR supporter. Stephens, Thomas: 1962-1968, 1968 Campaign, personal correspondence. Stevens, Danid H.: 1962, seeks appointment with NAR, personal correspondence. Stevens, Marion Lee: 1963, thanks to NAR. Stevens, Mary: 1967, Assistant to the Editor, "Foreign Affairs," NAR article & payment. Stevens, Robert: 1968, President, J.P. Stevens & Company, Governor of Minnesota and legal case. Stevenson, Charles: 1959, thanks to NAR. Stewart, B. A.: 1963, send "National Geographic" photos of upstate New York. Stewart, Richard: 1965-1966, NAR thanks. Stichman, Herman T.: 1963, Judson Morhouse investigation. Stiles, James: 1959, NAR thanks. Stone, Doris Zemurray: 1959, seeks appointment to see NAR. Stone, Fred L.: 1967, Vice President, Harris Trust & Savings Bank, NAR appearance on The Tonight Show. Stone, James H.: 1968, Stone Oil Company. Storey, N. W.: 1963, Manager, Phoenix County Club, sends photos. Stout, William (Mrs.): 1967, Williamsburg visit. Stratton, William G.: 1959, Governor of Illinois. Straud, W.B.D. (Mr. & Mrs.): 1970, NAR thanks. Strauss, Lewis: 1959, Senate action. Strickland, Stephen P.: 1968, Committee on White House Fellows, program & activities. Stuart D. Gregory: 1961, Gorman-Griffing, Inc., personnel, seeks recommendation on former employee. Stutz, Caryl & Ronald: 1961, thanks to NAR for wedding gift. Summerfield, Arthur E.: 1959, U.S. Postmaster General, sends commemorative stamps. Suter, Charles A.: 1968, President, Geigy Chemical Corporation, NAR thanks. Sweet, Robert W.: 1969, Deputy Mayor, New York City, advance to 1965 Lindsay campaign. Swezey, Kenneth M.: 1959, NAR thanks.
- Sable, Jack, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 422)
  Office for Community Afffairs, Human Rights.
- Samuels, Marvin (Dr.), 1958 (Box 19, Folder 423)
  Gubernatorial campaign.
- Savell, Isabelle, 1961-1971 (Box 19, Folder 424)
  Executive Mansion staff, Workmen's Compensation Board.
- Schenk, Benjamin, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 425)
  State Insurance Department Personnel.
- Scherer, Ray, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 426)
  National Broadcasting Corporation (NBC) correspondent in London, help for a newsman.
- Schneebeli, Herman, 1960-1970 (Box 19, Folder 427)
  Pennsylvania Congressman, NAR 1960 contribution, 1970 primary fight.
- Schroeder, Albert, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 428)
  NAR trip to Santa Fe.
- Schuler, Raymond T., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 429)
  Bond issue, public transportation, Regional Plan Association.
- Schwenk, Edwin M., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 430)
  Boyd for Congress Campaign.
- Scott, Hugh, 1964-1973 (Box 19, Folder 431)
  United States Senator from Pennsylvania, Minority Leader, 1964 Republican Convention Speeches on Vietnam, Romney 1968 Campaign, Dartmouth recommendation.
- Scranton, William, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 432)
  Governor of Pennsylvania, 1964 Republican Convention, Anti-Goldwater activity, 1966 speeches on Vietnam.
- Scribner, Fred C., Jr., 1966 (Box 19, Folder 433)
  Dartmouth reunion.
- Scrivner, Robert W., 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 434)
  Regional Plan Association, Rockefeller Brothers Fund.
- Scully, William (Most Reverend), 1959 (Box 19, Folder 435)
  Birth control.
- Secundina, Tony, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 436)
  Illness.
- Shanley, Bernard, 1959-1969 (Box 19, Folder 437)
  New Jersey Republican National Committeeman, New Jersey & international politics.
- Shapiro, Rose, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 438)
  Assistant to the Governor for Narcotics Education, Programs, seeks state job.
- Shapp, Milton, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 439)
  Governor of Pennsylvania, bicentennial celebration of First Continental Congress.
- Sheffield, Joseph, 1966-1969 (Box 19, Folder 440)
  Chairman, Governor's Club.
- Shientang, Florence P., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 442)
  Judge, politics.
- Silver, Edward, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 443)
  Member, New York State Commission of Investigation.
- Simon, Caroline, 1959-1967 (Box 19, Folder 444)
  North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 12 month school year, appointment to Court of Claims.
- Simpson, Frank (Mr. & Mrs.), 1959-1971 (Box 19, Folder 445)
  Muscular Dystrophy Drive, other charity drives, death of Frank Simpson.
- Slater, Ilene, 1959-1972 (Box 19, Folder 446)
  1960 Presidential campaign, "U.S. News" article, law school.
- Smith, A. Kendall (Reverend), 1972 (Box 19, Folder 447)
  Council of Churches, New York City Task Force on Racism.
- Smith, Marshall L. (Dr.), 1964-1973 (Box 19, Folder 448)
  Minister, Union Church of Pocantico Hills, personal, copies of sermons.
- Smith, Timothy G., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 449)
  NAR visit to University of Virginia Law School.
- Snyder, Patricia B., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 450)
  Director of Childrens Theater, State University of New York at Albany, NAR appearance at conference.
- Spad, Carl, 1959-1966 (Box 19, Folder 451)
  New York State Republican State Chairman, politics, appointments, election candidacies.
- Spencer, William, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 453)
  President, First National City Bank, dinner for the President of Mexico.